<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<!--EUREKA====================================================-->
       
		<string-array name="tpp">
        <item >
            Every gadget has a story. Explore technology as never before with lucid explanations on the working and applications of TPP is a foremost pedestal for empowering ideas to reality through technical papers presented by students from various fields to industry professionals. Students with technical know-how and a desire to change the world by providing extensive and well thought over solutions to general problems will have to draft white papers on the respective topics. Elite judges from several professional streams will review the deliverables and help implement brilliant solutions.
For most of us from a science background, it is always appreciable to have done some research on a certain topic and present it in the best way possible. Technical Paper Presentation (TPP) is a platform which allows you to do so. A technical presentation is a writing of the method of research, the research findings and the creation of information on the technical process of a product or service.

\nTEAM SPECIFICATION:
\nA team may consist of a maximum of 2 participants. Students from different educational institutes can form a team.

\nCERTIFICATE POLICY:
\n1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of excellence will be given to top three teams.
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.

\nCash Prize of 12,000 INR to be won.
\nCertificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.
         </item>
        <item> 
 	
            		 1. Choose a topic that interests you the most and one which you will find feasible to present as a 
     technical paper with adequate research information to substantiate.
\n2. Prepare a abstract about your paper and mail it to us.
\n3. We will assess your presentation and let you know if you are qualified for the final round during 
     Technovanza
\n4. If you are shortlisted you will be given a chance to present your paper during Technovanza 2013
Teams have to send their abstract for Technical Paper Presentation with their Team name on tpp@technovanza.org on or before 20th December, 2013.     
    	</item>
        <item >
            a. Presentation cannot exceed 10 minutes with additional 2-3 minutes of queries
\nb. The paper must be presented in single-spaced size 12 Times New Roman or Arial font. The matter should have direct correlation to the selected topic.
\nc. Any graphs, tables, charts, pictures and other illustrations shall be counted in the 6 page limit. Topics, table of contents and the bibliography will not be counted under the 6 page limit.
\nd. Papers which do not mention the sourced content in either the footnotes or the bibliography will be disqualified on account of plagiarism
\ne. Maximum of 2 participants can form a team in TPP.
\nf. One can present their technical paper based on any topic.
            
        </item>
        <item >Akshay Alse	+91 7666863708
\nRadhika Padmanabhan +91 9920901059
            
        </item>
        <item>
            specification,judging criteria,tutorials,and much more.... \n.on http://technovanza.org/tpp.php
        </item>
        </string-array>
				
		<string-array name="hsw">
        <item >
           Every gadget has a story. Explore technology as never before with lucid explanations on the working and applications of some of the most commonly used devices! Ranging from 3D technology to signal automation to the latest play stations and x-boxes, unveil the insides of our present day systems. We live in a world that has got its mysteries, facts, innovations that amaze us in the most unpredictable ways. Rediscover a new dimension to your curiosity and understanding of the underlying. Unleash the awe of detail and intricacy of the much advanced and prevalent technologies.
How stuff works in Technovanza is yet another way to bring about a way to give an insight to those who are intrigued by stuff happening around them. It’s always good to know, isn’t it?
\nTEAM SPECIFICATION :
\nA team may consist of a maximum of 6 participants. Students from different educational institutes can form a team.

\nCERTIFICATE POLICY:
\n1.  Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of excellence will be given to top three teams.
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.
\nCash Prize of 5,000 INR to be won. 
\nCertificates will be given on the spot. 
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.        
         </item>
        <item> 
 			 1.  Discuss with your team-mates and choose a topic that interests you the most. Remember, whatever you choose must already exist.
\n2.  Prepare a power point presentation briefly describing how you will go about your project on the topic you have chosen. Be specific in your ideas you want to implement.
\n3.  Send your presentation to us and we will assess you on the basis of how good and efficient your project is.
\n4.  If you are selected your project is on display during Technovanza.
\nTeams have to send their presentation of their projects for How Stuff Works? with their Team name on hsw@technovanza.org on or before 30th November, 2013. 
Teams also have to send the video of their working model on the above mail-id by 25th of December, 2013.     
    	</item>
        <item >
            1.  Applicable only to First Year students.
\n2.  The idea for working model of your project is expected in your presentation.
\n3.  The working model should fit into the size of 6ft. by 6 ft. of the stall size.
            
        </item>
        <item >Laeena Kottwani +91 9619451482
\nHena Shah +91 9029967487 
\nPrapti Verma +91 9930874381
            
        </item>
        <item>
            specification,judging criteria,tutorials,and much more.... \n.on http://technovanza.org/hsw.php
        </item>
        </string-array>
		
		<string-array name="xcon">
        <item >
            Showcase your projects and exhibits in diverse fields in X-CON. Ranging from robotics to civil exhibits to mechanical projects and physics experiments, view the most exciting and innovating works of students from various grades. It is a platform to empower students to convert their ideas to reality and win exciting prizes and gain immense recognition for their efforts and creation through this best exhibit contest. Redesigning the future through their projects, students make a significant contribution to society globally and win accolades for their work. Integrating the past, the present and the future technologies, exhibitions bring together creative, stylized, implementable and sustainable technological solutions for society. 
\nTEAM SPECIFICATION :
\nA team may consist of a maximum of 6 participants. Students from different educational institutes can form a team.
\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of excellence will be given to top three teams. 
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.
\nCash Prize of 10,500 INR to be won.
\nCertificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions. 
        </item>
        <item> 
 			 a.	Decide the topic based on which you would like to make your project/ exhibit on. Choose a topic which interests you the most and which you will be able to present in the most efficient manner.
\nb.	If your project is approved it will be showcased as an exhibit during Technovanza 2013!! 


\nTeams have to send their proposal of their projects for X-Con with their Team name on operations@technovanza.org on or before 30th November, 2013.
\nTeams also have to send the video of their working model on the above mail-id by 25th of December, 2013.       
    	</item>
        <item >1.	Applicable to all college students with proper identity-cards.
\n2.	The idea for working model of your project is expected in your proposal.
\n3.	The working model should fit into the size of 8ft. by 8 ft. of the stall size. If needed more please let us know much before the design.
            
        </item>
        <item >Shreeya Laad -	+91 9833256744.</item>
        <item>
            specification,judging criteria,tutorials,and much more.... \n.on http://technovanza.org/x-con.php
        </item>
        </string-array>
		
				<string-array name="rcmo">
        
           <item > Are you one of those guys who roam around with the Rubiks Cube in your pocket all the time, struggling to beat the clock all the time??struggling for your best even though you have just achieved it?? Getting nightmare about the parity?? Trying to hit stack mat pads, without having a stack mat next to you!??...having a cube right in front of you while you read this??
This is the place to showcase your skills with the Magic Cube. Following the last 4 years tremendous success Technovanza in association with the World Cube Association (WCA), for the 5th time in VJTI, Mumbai, will set a stage for one of the largest cubing event\competition in the country. This competition brings the citys finest solvers together on one platform. A world class competition and a truly phenomenal one. Welcoming all the “CUBERS” around the globe...
The RCBO along with World Cube Association governs competitions for all puzzles labelled as Rubik puzzles, and all other puzzles that are played by twisting the sides, so-called twisty puzzles. Most famous of these puzzles is the Rubiks Cube, invented by professor Rubik from Hungary. More positions than you have brain cells.
The goal of the RCBO is to have more competitions with more people and more fun, under fair conditions. The spirit of this competition is that people from all over the world have fun together in a friendly atmosphere, help each other and inculcate a spirit of sportsman-ship in them. Rubik’s Cube Mumbai Open is our flagship event from last 4 years and this time it is going to be bigger and even better. RCBO has always been a major attraction with a large foot over and one of the biggest hit of Technovanza, and so are we expecting it this year. So get ready to witness "speed cubing" like you have never done before !! The World Cube Association record books beckon you.. So what are you waiting for ? Bring out those cubes and start cubing !!
VJTI and Technovanza are proud to present it.
\nThe event details and schedule will be put as soon as possible, and the schedule may change according to the number of participants.
\nBEWARE: Some of these guys can solve the cube, blindfolded.
You turn it and it will twist you!!
\nHappy Cubing!

\n\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of excellence will be given to the winners.
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.       
         </item>
        <item> 
 			 Events:
\n•	2x2x2
\n•	3x3x3
\n•	3x3x3 - one hand
\n•	3x3x3 - blindfolded
\n•	4x4x4
\n•	5x5x5
\n•	6x6x6
\n•	7x7x7
\n•	Pyraminx
\n•	Megaminx
\n•	Square 1
\n...More to be added later    
    	</item>
        <item >The competitions strictly follows the World Cube Associations rules</item>
        <item >Pratik Poojary +91 9022228882</item>
        <item>
            specification,judging criteria,tutorials,and much more.... \n.on http://technovanza.org/rcmo.php
        </item>
        </string-array>
		
		<string-array name="junior_xcon">
        <item >
          Little minds are the most creative and hence, we here at Technovanza give an opportunity to those budding Einsteins to showcase their creativity and curiosity in the form of projects they have made. Junior XCON is thus an initiative to harness and nurture young talent, it is a contest for school students to project their ideas and knowledge through working models accompanied by lucid explanations during the 3 days of Technovanza. Several robotic endeavors, mechanical crusades and projects based on physics, chemistry and school sciences have given impetus to young minds to realize theoretical concepts and provide a thundering new dimension to their thinking and scale their abilities to a height unimagined before 

\nTEAM SPECIFICATION:
\nA team may consist of a maximum of 5 participants. Students from different educational institutes can form a team.

\nCERTIFICATE POLICY:
\n1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of excellence will be given to top three teams.
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates

\nCash Prize worth 5,000 INR to be won.
\nCertificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions   
          </item>
        <item> 
 			 1.  Discuss with your team-mates and choose a topic that interests you the most.
\n2.  Prepare a power point presentation briefly describing how you will go about your project on the topic you have chosen. Be specific in your ideas you want to implement.
\n3.  Send your presentation to us and we will assess you on the basis of how good and efficient your project is.
\n4.  If you are selected your project is on display during Technovanza 2013.

\nTeams have to send their presentation of their projects for Junior X-Con with their Team name on jxcon@technovanza.org on or before 20th December, 2013.        
    	</item>
        <item >Following is the schedule for the 3 days (6th to 8th January) of Technovanza’13.
   \na. Timing of exhibition: 10.30 am to 4.30 pm
  \n b. Morning Slot: 10.30 am to 1.00 pm 
   \nc. Lunch break: 1 pm to 2 pm
   \nd. Afternoon slot: 2 pm to 4.30 pm

\n1.  Applicable only to school students.
\n2.  One teacher may accompany the students presenting the projects.
\n3.  All the facilities needed to exhibit the projects will be provided to the students.
\n4.  The responsibility of bringing students and taking them back safely would be on the school.
\n5.  Parking facility is unavailable within the campus but available outside it.</item>
        <item >
            Shreya Shah +91 7666506698 
\nKanchi Masalia +91 9773778527
            
        </item>
        <item>
            specification,judging criteria,tutorials,and much more.... \n.on http://technovanza.org/junior-xcon.php
        </item>
        </string-array>
        
		<string-array name="contraption">
        <item >
            If you thought technology is all about reducing effort and simplifying life, then here\'s your chance to witness its role reversal – CONTRAPTION as the smallest tasks are completed through complex, twisted, impossible, weird and intelligent routes! ! Year after year this event leaves spectators mystified, filling their hearts with unmatched excitement and wonder with each step! An experience not worth missing!
         </item>
        <item> 
 			 coming soon!!
    	</item>
        <item >
            coming soon!!!
        </item>
        <item >
            coming soon!!!
         </item>
        <item>
            specification,judging criteria,tutorials,and much more.... \n.on http://technovanza.org/contraption.php
        </item>
        </string-array>
		
        
	
		</resources>
        
