<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<!--ibuild==================================================== -->
		
		<string-array name="BridgetheGap">
        <item >
		\nIntroduction
\nAcross gulfs and rivers, between peoples and countries, bridges break down separation and foster connectedness. As far back as we can see in history, human beings have used technology to solve problems and ease physical burdens, suspension bridges have played a major role in human development….spanning over great lengths!!! Here is your chance to build a similar structure with your own techniques and skills and show the world the marvels of engineering!!

\nTEAM SPECIFICATION:
\nA team may consist of a maximum of 3 participants. Students from different educational institutes can form a team.

\nCERTIFICATE POLICY:
1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of excellence will be given to top three teams.
2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates

\nCash Prize of 4,000 INR to be won.
\nCertificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.

            </item>
			
        <item> 
\n\Think yourself to be a sound civil engineer??? Its time to prove it!!! Technovanza brings you the challenge to design and construct a model of a Suspension Bridge out of Popsicle sticks that would not collapse under the heaviest of the loads and at the same time satisfy the given constraints. An event promised to set you to jitters and put your engineering skills at stake!!

    	</item>
        <item >
		\nStructural Specifications:
\nA)  The deck of the bridge should be minimum 1 m in length.
\nB)  The width of the deck should not be less than 8 cm.
\nC)  There should be only two towers.
\nD)  The deck should not be having any kind of support except the support provided by the given towers. The deck should be purely hanging between the two towers.

\nMaterial Specifications:
\nA)  All materials required to construct the structures will be provided by the organizers. Any team found using any other material than that provided will be disqualified.
\nB)  Maximum length of the thread to be used is 8 m.

\nTime Constraint:
\nA)  The event would be one day long
\nB)  Contestants will be given a total of 5hrs for the competition.
		</item>
        <item >
		Isha Shah +91 9892063359\n
Khemraj Kubal +91 8097820870
		</item>
        <item >specification,judging criteria,tutorials,and much more.... \n.on http://technovanza.org/bridge-the-gap.php</item>
    </string-array>
    
	<string-array name="drive_thru">
        <item > 
\nIntroduction
\nA race against time! Drive thru" is the complete test of a varied amalgamation of civil engineering problems! Complete all obstacles in a given time and drive thru"! 
\nTEAM SPECIFICATION :
\nA team may consist of a maximum of 4 participants. 
\nStudents from different educational institutes can form a team.
\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of excellence will be given to top three teams. 
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.

\nCash Prize of 10,000 INR to be won.
\nCertificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.

        </item>

        <item> 
 \n					It is a very simple event of just travelling through a given route and reaching the destination.
\n 	In this route, participants will come across various obstructions.
 \n	Participants will have to construct different civil related structures so as to come over the obstructions.
 \n	The structures must be efficient and technically designed by the participants.
 \n	The structure must be such that a vehicle can pass through it.
 \n	The event will be a two day event.
 \n	On each day, participants will be given 3hrs of time.
 \n	After the completion of 6 hrs, judging process will start which will be strictly confidential and cannot be challenged by anyone.
    	</item>

        <item >
	\n	 	All materials required to construct the structures will be provided by the organization. Any group found using other material will be disqualified.
 	\nContestants will have to carry their own calculators for the event, if needed.
 	\nMinimum 2 and Maximum 4 members are allowed in one group.
 	\nContestants will be given a total of 6 hrs, i.e. 3 hrs on first day and another 3 hrs on second day of the event.
		</item>

        <item >
		\nRaju Kadam -	+918898848496
		\nParth Savla -	 +919004868252

		</item>

        <item >specification,judging criteria,tutorials,and much more.... \n.on http://technovanza.org/drive-thru.php</item>
    </string-array>
    
</resources>