<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<!--imech==================================================== -->
		<string-array name="ClimbeRope">
        <item >
		
		Here’s the rope to success! Can your bot climb it?? But here’s the twist 
		a bot has to climb the rope using any hydraulic mechanism which could
		be as simple as a syringe. \n
		\nTEAM SPECIFICATION : \nA team may consist of a maximum of 4 participants. 
		Students from different educational institutes can form a team.
		\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: \n1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of excellence will be given to top three teams. 
		\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates. 
		\nCash Prizes of 3000 INR to be won. Certificates will be given on the spot.
		\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.
        </item>
        <item> 
 				A team may consist of a maximum of 3 participants. Students from different colleges can form a team. 
\nThe team that performs any acts that are not in the spirit of fair play or the team which fails to obey instructions or warnings will be disqualified. 

\nFIRST ROUND: 
\n1. The bot has to climb vertically upwards against gravity. 
\n2. The bot must reach the top in least time. 

\nSECOND ROUND: 
\n1. The top five teams will compete against each another in a race format. 
\n2. The race would be on an incined rope. 
\n3. The team that reaches to the flag in least time wins. 
  
    	</item>
		
        <item >
		GAME RULES: 
\n1. The bot should be based on hydrolic mechanism only. 
\n2. If the bot topples or falls from its path i.e.the rope,it will be allowed to take a restart but from starting the point. 
\n3. However the timer will not stop. 
\n4. The bot cannot be made up of any electrical devices or components e.g.motors. 
\n5. If found using so, the team will be disqualified. 

		</item>
		
        <item >Shubham Kathalkar \t+91 9665361191\n Tushar Rathod \t+91 9922592093</item>
		
		<item >specification,judging criteria,tutorials,and much more.... \n.on http://technovanza.org/climb-e-rope.php</item>
    </string-array>
    
	 <string-array name="fastandfurious">
        <item >
            INTRODUCTION:\n
 \nDesign the fastest and the shrewdest IC engine car and put on your set-belts to face a white-knuckling race through the roughest arena! From the makers of ‘Split-Second’ here’s another thrilling real time all-terrain racing competition, race the fast and the furious from across the nation! Let’s put your car-designing abilities and your car’s the strength, power and efficiency of to test. 
\nTEAM SPECIFICATION :
\nA team may consist of  maximum  5 participants. A team may have students from different educational institutes.
\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to all the teams and certificate of   excellence will be given to only the top three teams. 
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be awarded certificates.
\nCash Prize of 45,000 INR to be won.
 \nCertificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.

            
         </item>
		 
        <item> 
 			  
			  Make a wireless remote controlled machine, powered by only an IC engine, which can race against other opponents on an off-road dirt track with many obstacles.
\nTeams have to send their abstract of their robots for Fast AND Furious  with their Team name and Team Leader on operations@technovanza.org on or before 15th October, 2013.
\nTeams also have to send the video of their working model on the above mail-id by 25th of December, 2013.
    	</item>
		
		
        <item >
		\nQualifying round :-
\n\t•	 Each participating team will get only two laps with a gap of maximum 5 minutes between each lap! The fastest lap will be considered!
\n\t•	 Not more than 2 team members will be allowed in the arena at a time.
\n\t•	The top teams from the qualifying rounds will make it to the second round.
	\nSecond round
\n\t•	Races will be conducted between multiple cars at a time. The participants must use a remote with frequency of band spectrum 2.4 GHz, ensuring that the frequency of your remote does not overlap with others. 
\n\t•	In the final round only one of the team members will be allowed in the racing arena other than the controller on the stand.
\n\t•	Checkpoints will be placed throughout the arena.
\n\t•	If a machine is stuck or falls off the arena, that team will be allowed to pick it up and place it at a checkpoint behind that point, the time for which will be added to the total lap time.
\n\t•	If a machine disintegrates in the arena leaving behind loose parts the team will be disqualified.
\n\t•	Once the race begins team members will be immediately disqualified if found touching their`s or opponent`s machine.
\n\t•	If any of the bots starts off before the flag is waved, the counter would be restarted and the machines will get a second chance. However, if any machine starts off before the waving of flag (or countdown) for a second time, it will be disqualified. Once disqualified the team can`t participate again in the event. .
\n\t•	If any member of a team is found purposely damaging other team`s bot the team will be disqualified.

		</item>
		
        <item >
		Aman Jha	\t+91 7709081462
		</item>   
		
		<item >specification,judging criteria,tutorials,and much more.... \n.on http://technovanza.org/fast-furious.php</item>
  </string-array>
    
    </resources>