<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

		<!-- impulse==================================================== -->
		<string-array name="TrickyTronics">
        <item >
            Identify components, assemble circuits,
             test your electronics in this impulsive and hands on event.
         </item>
        <item> 
 				Coming soon!!!     
    	</item>
        <item >Coming soon!!!</item>
        <item >Archana Dhum : 7208280625\n
Bhagyashri Patere : 9773793652</item>
    </string-array>
    
		<string-array name="lan_gamimg">
        <item >Hushed voices, silent footsteps, reloading of a gun, reviving of engines, a gush of nitrous .If this is your 
kind of music, then this is your kind of event! For all those gaming maniacs who can’t get enough of the 
virtual world! An event promising excitement, pressure, thrill and enjoyment to the core! Where the 
virtual will merge into reality, the ultimate LAN gaming experience awaits the worthy challengers! 
         </item>
        <item> 
 				Coming soon!!!     
    	</item>
        <item >Coming soon!!!</item>
        <item >Srinath Umbarje : 9594845524</item>
    </string-array>
   <string-array name="TextoMania">
        <item >
            If mozart can play the piano blind, shouldn’t the computer
             addicts be able to type blindfolded! Lets see…
         </item>
        <item> 
 				Coming soon!!!     
    	</item>
        <item >Coming soon!!!</item>
        <item >Anita Trimukhe : 7208296366</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ClickNCapture">
        <item >
            Look at the various events in Technovanza’13 and 
            capture your favourite sectors onto a collage in photoshop.
             Tickle your creative side, photography, designing ability and
              your eye for observation altogether with this on spot challenge.
         </item>
        <item> 
 				Coming soon!!!     
    	</item>
        <item >Coming soon!!!</item>
        <item >Hrishikesh Chowdhari : 9403511775</item>
    </string-array>   
    <string-array name="GoogleJunkie">
        <item >
            Enough of coding! Come and just Google!! 
            Google Junkie is a fun filled event which checks
             your capabilities in using the google search engine.
         </item>
        <item> 
 				Coming soon!!!     
    	</item>
        <item >Coming soon!!!</item>
        <item >Atul Nar : 8976844017</item>
    </string-array>   
    <string-array name="TechQuiz">
        <item >
            Passionate about the latest gadgets, well informed about
             the gods of technological inventions, aware of every bit of the techno world? 
             Explore your technological fascinaton and update your tech knowledge!
         </item>
        <item> 
 				Coming soon!!!     
    	</item>
        <item >Coming soon!!!</item>
        <item >Sameer Watve-8976271360\n
Pratik Pokharkar : 9004932690</item>
    </string-array>   
    <string-array name="tweet2win">
        <item >Online recharge is lot more fun and perky now, thanks to Technovanza+ Twitter! Its only here that a 
tweet is equal to Rs 100! Our tasks plus your cool quotient gets you a chance to win a free recharge! So get funky and crazy, amaze us with your talent by 
completing the wackiest tasks of the season and immediately tweet to win hash tagging Technovanza! Are you game? 
         </item>
        <item> 
 				Coming soon!!!     
    	</item>
        <item >Coming soon!!!</item>
        <item >Coming soon!!!</item>
    </string-array>   
    <string-array name="TechCharades">
        <item >
            Techno is ready to leave you speechless this time (literally)! 
            Forget movies how well can you enact technical words?
         </item>
        <item> 
 				Coming soon!!!     
    	</item>
        <item >Coming soon!!!</item>
        <item >Tejashri : 9422575981</item>
    </string-array>           
		
		</resources>