<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<!-- Manageria==================================================== -->
		<string-array name="UNICUS">
        <item >
            Do you see yourselves in the league of Ambani, Tata or Birla? Do you dream of becoming the next Carlos Slim (Richest man in the world) or Bill Gates? Have a big idea? Want to do something about it? We give you this wonderful opportunity to exhibit and showcase your business skills.
Our Business plan competition "UNICUS" is here. 
E-Cell’s National-level Business-Plan Competition in which participants have to submit their business plans for their entrepreneurial venture and the best plan gets mentorship and capital funding of up to 75000 INR

\nTEAM SPECIFICATION :
\nA team may consist of a maximum of 6 participants. Students from different educational institutes can 

form a team.
\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation or participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of excellence will be given to the winner. 
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.

\nThe best B-plan will receive a funding of maximum 1,00,000 INR on behalf of Entrepreneurship Cell.
\nThe best socially relevant B-plan will be awarded separately.
\nCertificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.
            
         </item>
        <item> 
 			 1st Round:
\nOnline questionnaire + Plan Description  
\nThe online portal for submissions will open latest by 1st October and will close by 20th October (subject to participation). The results will be declared in the first week of November and Mentorship program will commence.
\n2nd round:
\nThere will be a formal presentation consisting of one whole day and a winner will be decided.
\nAlso, a socially evident business plan stands a chance to be funded.
            
    	</item>
        <item >RULES AND LEGAL ISSUES:\n
The following rules are binding throughout the entire duration of the UNICUS Business Plan Competition. Participating in UNICUS indicates that teams accept these rules and regulations and agree to abide by them. UNICUS Business Plan Competition Student Management Committee reserve the right to disqualify any team and/or team member it believes is not abiding by the rules of the UNICUS.\n


\nELIGIBILITY\n
Students and Working Professionals from all over the country can participate.\n
Individual participation is allowed in the Competition though participation in teams is encouraged.\n
Though it must be noted that teams who have registered their company/startup before the span of last one year, are not eligible to participate in UNICUS 2013.\n
Entries must be the original work of entrants.\n

\nACCEPTABLE BUSINESS PLANS\n
Conventional and non-conventional plans are eligible for the competition, including, but not limited to:\n
New venture/new business (including non-profit businesses)\n
Merger or acquisition, including leveraged buyouts that will lead to a turnaround, roll-up, or some other significant change that adds value to the current business\n
Joint venture, alliance or network-based business (e.g., create new entity from current enterprises)\n
Licensing arrangements\n
Search funds\n
\n
Note that all businesses are judged based on the same criteria. A plan is not eligible if - before August 28th, 2013 - has earned more than 5,00,000 INR in gross revenue.\n
\n
The UNICUS Business Plan Competition Student Management Committee reserves the right to reject any business plan for reasons including, but not limited to:\n
\n
Deemed to be in violation of the Code Of Ethics\n 
Violates any local, state or national law and/or appears to be pornographic in nature\n
Was previously awarded a top prize (Grand, Second or Third) in the UNICUS Business Plan Competition\n
Does not present sufficient content or material appropriate to send to judges for evaluation and feedback\n
Does not follow the rules set forth by the UNICUS Business Plan Competition (i.e. page limits, etc.)\n
Does not meet the eligibility requirements of the UNICUS Business Plan Competition\n

        </item>
        <item >Aditya Narayanan  	+91 9594235049
\nPrajakta Padalwar  	+91 9167949892
\nAditi Patange  		+91 9969041457
            
        </item>
        <item>for more information visit: http://technovanza.org/unicus.php</item>
        </string-array>
		
		<string-array name="HIRE">
        <item >
            Ever thought what it is actually working hands-on in a company especially in its core committee? Wanted to make decisions and have people work under you? Here we provide you that very chance; an HR Management event! You can head a company and manage it to glory!
A National-level Human Resource Management E-Cell event, wherein participants are given the opportunity to be an HR-Manager or employee  of an enterprise which would be a one day Business-Venture and thus manage the human resource of his enterprise.

\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of   excellence will be given to top two teams. 
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.
\nCash Prize of 20,000 INR to be won.
\n Certificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.
        </item>
        <item> 
 			 HIRE is a 1-day event. Applications for applying as managers are published. All the selected managers for each sector will interview and HIRE employees for their companies. The final team executes as per their respective sectors and performs in a stipulated time frame, on one of the 3 days of Technovanza, the annual Techno-Managerial festival of VJTI. The winners will judged by business professionals based on an overall performance.

The entire event consists of 3 parts.
\n1.	The applications for HR managers are put up. 2 problem statements are given. The applicants are expected to provide a feasible business solution/ model for the problem statements. All the solutions will be judged by an expert team from E-Cell, VJTI. Parameters like – business sustainability, financial planning, HR management, creativity and common sense will be considered. HR managers will be given their sector preference according to the scores. 2 HR managers will be selected per sector.

\n2.	An interview round will be taken in VJTI for employees inside the VJTI campus on a given pre-informed date. The HR recruits 5 members for each sector.

\n3.	On a given day of Technovanza, the annual Techno-Managerial festival of VJTI the HR teams play out with each other in a given time slot. Each sector gives a presentation on the entire project touching points like finance, ideas and efforts. Distinguished judges from the industry judge the winner. Points like profit, ideas, management skills and marketing to be taken into consideration. Cash prizes for the top 2 sectors.
            
    	</item>
        <item >Part 1:
\n1.	HR managers can be from any college. (Except 1st years).
\n2.	Plagiarism for the solutions of problem statements will not be tolerated.
\n3.	The HR managers should come up with a Name for their sector’s company.
\n4.	Managers have to be ready with brief idea of their sector’s company for the interviews..

\nPart 2:
\n1.	HR managers have to present compulsorily for the interviews.
\n2.	The interviews will be completely transparent. Only the people present for the interview can be HIREd.
\n3.	The interviewees can be from any college.

\nPart 3:
\n1.	The HR managers will be given Rs. 2500 as initial start-up money which has to be returned at the end.
\n2.	The HR managers should submit their space, electricity and other such requirements to the event heads beforehand.
\n3.	Companies would be allotted stalls. Entire business to be executed from the prescribed stalls only.
\n4.	HRs should not conduct an event from any other sector than theirs.
\n5.	Companies can start publicizing their events 1 week before the event. Any known publicity before can lead to disqualification.
\n6.	The entire presentation is expected to be transparent. Any misleading facts during the final presentation could lead to disqualification.
\n7.	Only the HIREd employees can conduct the event on that day. Inclusion of any other team member is not allowed.
\n8.	Event to be executed in E-Cell, VJTI official t-shirts only. 
            
        </item>
        <item >Priyanka Bharati +91 961923045
\nSwadhin Thakkar +91 9869287199
            
        </item>
        <item>for more information visit: http://technovanza.org/hire.php</item>
		
        </string-array>
		<string-array name="Wallstreet">
        <item >
            Warren Buffet (Chairman and CEO of Berkshire Hathaway) one of the richest men in the world bought his first stocks at a meager age of 11! Now he is one of the most respected man in the world. Do you think you have what it takes to make it big with stocks? Here we present you a virtual stock market trade for skilled investors

\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of   excellence will be given to the winner. 
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.
\nCash Prize of 12,000 INR to be won.
\n Certificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.
            
         </item>
        <item> 
 			 As the name suggests, it is E-Cell’s Virtual Stock Market wherein the participants can trade in stocks, real-estate, commodities, currencies etc. with the sole objective of maximizing their profits in accordance with the market index by the closing-bell of our Virtual Stock Market.
The event is based on the stock market or stock stimulator but by using virtual money.
The contestants will practice trading real stocks, ETFs, and mutual funds using real-time market prices for a time-span of atleast 6 hours.
There would be news flashes in every short interval which will affect the nominal and market values of the stocks and  the contestants are expected to wisely buy or sell their stocks respectively.
The contestant having the highest profit margin will be declared as the ultimate "BULL" of the market and also be rewarded.
            </item>
        <item >1.	The participants are expected to start their transactions only by the opening bell of the market and end the game by the closing bell.
\n2.	It will be an individual event.
            
        </item>
        <item >Fatema Lokhandwala 		+91 8976559491
\nRavindra Jain			 +91 9967731387
            
        </item>
        <item>for more information visit: http://technovanza.org/wallstreet.php</item>
        </string-array>
		
		<string-array name="Consultant">
        <item >
            Do problems interest you? Do you think you can solve some of the most complex business problems? So here is The Consultant, all set to test your analytical skills, reasoning and will to convert every problem into a road to success and profits! We invite all the budding consultants to put on their thinking caps and get ready to face the challenges of the industry! 
            TEAM SPECIFICATION :.
A team may consist of a maximum of 3 participants. Students from different educational institutes can form a team.
\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation or participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of   excellence will be given to top two teams. 
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.
\nCash Prize of 15,000 INR to be won.
\n Certificates will be given on the spot.
FREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.
            
         </item>
        <item> 
 			 As such, THE CONSULTANT is E-Cell’s Managerial-Problem Tackling event which follows a case study structure. In which participants would have to tackle various crisis faced by corporate entities and come up with most innovative and effective solutions to avert the crisis.
Explore the inside of the business world, acting as pseudo-consultants to real organizations for a day! Come be a consultant!

Event is of three rounds:-

\nRound 1 
\n3 problem statements will be  given , each team have to choose anyone of the  problem statement and provide the appropriate solution to it.The team which provides correct solution will be selected and at the end of round 1 10 teams will be selected.


\nRound 2
\n10 teams selected from round 1 once again will have 2 solve problem statement which will be relatively difficult than round 1 .But in this round participant wont choose the problem statement on there own.They  will have to provide solution to that problem statement which we give to them.Two teams will have to find appropriate solution for a common problem statement , from that two team only one team will be selected.In this manner 10 teams will be divided in 5 groups and from each group one team will be selected.At the end of round 2 we get top 5 team which enters final round i.e round 3.


\nRound 3
\nIn final round, the teams will get a real-time exposure of a particular company and will be introduced to the problem faced by that company.
They will have to prepare a presentation of their solution and present it in front of the judges.
And the best one wins.
            
    	</item>
        <item >Coming soon!!!</item>
        <item >Roshini Rathod		+91 9967990507
\nGauri Kamthe 			+91 9619008792
            
        </item>
        <item>for more information visit: http://technovanza.org/consultant.php</item>
        </string-array>
		
		<string-array name="Freakonomics">
        <item >
            E-Cell VJTI has also taken an initiative this year to revive its event FREAKONOMICS, so that oratorical speaking-an integral part of a manager’s life is not left unpolished. 
FREAKONOMICS is a simulation of the parliamentary procedure, with participants dealing with questions befetting our policy-makers and providing solutions for divisive issues.
In order to acquaint oneself with the economic on-goings of the country, E-CELL, VJTI has re-introduced this event with the insight of giving all the economic enthusiasts, with a passion for politics, an opportunity to put forth their opinions and debating skills.

\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of   excellence will be given to the winner. 
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.
\nCash Prize of 6000 INR to be won.
\n Certificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.
            
         </item>
        <item> 
 			 Round 1: Debate round
\nThe ten teams would be split up into groups of 5 teams each and a parliamentary issue would be given to the teams (1 group would speak in favour and the other in against) and they have to debate on that . (15 mins)5 teams would be shortlisted.

\nRound 2 –Impromptu round.
\nNow, the participants will be competing with each other on an individual basis.
They will be given some relevant Economic topics and are expected to speak on that particular topic. (Speechlimit – 3mins)

\nRound 3- Opine your views.
\nEach participant will now be given the opportunity to speak for/against what other participants’ speech.  He/she is also expected to give the most apt solution according to him/her.
            
    	</item>
        <item >\n1.	Use of Mobile phones is strictly prohibited at the venue of event.
\n2.	The participants are expected to maintain their composure during the entire tenure of the event, any heated disputes will lead to his/her disqualification.
\n3.	Also, the decision of the event heads will be given first preference in this scenario
            
        </item>
        <item >Bhakti Dalvi 		+91 9769649637
\nSwarashri Chaudhari 	+91 9503763024
            
        </item>
        <item>for more information visit: http://technovanza.org/freakonomics.php</item>
        </string-array>
		
		<string-array name="Bizquiz">
        <item >
            Your friends consider you a know-it-all? Especially about the news in the corporate world? Then this is the place for you to match your wits against many who show the same enthusiasm! 

\nTEAM SPECIFICATION :
\nA team may consist of a maximum of 2 participants. Students from different educational institutes can form a team.
\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation/participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of   excellence will be given to the winner. 
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.
\nCash Prize of 6000 INR to be won.
\n Certificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.
            
         </item>
        <item> 
Round 1 (THEORY QUIZ)
\nParticipants will be given a sheet of questionnaire, cut off will be set and all the participants who are able to score above that will be selected. Around 25 participants will qualify for the  round 2.

\nRound 2 (LOGO QUIZ)
\nParticipants will be divided in a group of 5 members, so that 5 teams are formed. All the teams will be shown a logo on the projector and whichever team is able to get it right, will get points, which will add on their individual scores that they have scored in the written test. Lowest scoring 3 teams will get eliminated and thus we will have 10 contestants for the next round. Teams will be decided on lucky draw basis.
\nRound 3(RAPID FIRE)
\nThe quizzer will be asking questions to participants who are divided in a group of 2 members. So we will be having 5 teams who will answer the questions. Lowest scoring 3 teams will get eliminated and hence we will have 4 participants for the next round and the respective points will be added to the participants previous score.
\nRound 4(CHALLENGE ROUND)
\nThe participants will be asked to devise questions for each other and whosoever answers the question right will get points and the winner and the runner-up will be thus decided on the basis of points earned by each participant. 
            
    	</item>
        <item >\n1.	Participants will not be allowed to carry books, mobile phones, laptops or any other electronic gadgets at the site of the event.
\n2.	The Participants should be in teams of two and should be pursuing to Undero or Post Graduate Degree.
\n3.	In case of any disputes among the individuals or teams, the decision of the quizzer and the event heads will be taken into account.
            
        </item>
        <item >Prachi Koti  	+91 9920902324
\nKritikaKatre 	 +91 8983205307

            
        </item>
        <item>for more information visit: http://technovanza.org/biz-quiz.php</item>
        </string-array>
		
		
		<string-array name="SCAM">
        <item >
            S.C.a.M is a managerial event that tests you with your business skills. This event gets you on a ride with three main aspects of a venture - Selling, Convincing and Marketing (S.C.a.M). Become the numerouno in your business venture!

\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation or participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of   excellence will be given to winner and runner-up. 
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.
\nCash Prize of 8000 INR to be won.
\nCertificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.
            
         </item>
        <item> 
 			 S.C.a.M    stands   for selling,   convincing   and   marketing.  There will be three rounds- 1st for selling,2nd for convincing and 3rd is for marketing. As the name suggests, in this event, participants will get knowledge about how to sell and get profit from the customers(in this case generally students), also the way of convincing the students for doing the task, and the marketing skills.
The contestants would be judged on their ability to formulate strategy, their bargaining skills and the way they make a mark in an unknown market.
\nSELLING -   Selling is the first round of this event. This round will be conducted individually. In this round, the participants will be given any uncommon products or commodities. They are expected to sell those products at a price higher than the MRP and gain maximum profit out of it.
\nCONVINCING- Convincing is the second round of scam. The participants whoclear the first round will be shortlisted for this round. They will be subjected to some management tasks and will have to convince the crowd to implement them.

\nMARKETING- Marketing is the third and last round of this event. The participants will be handed a certain amount of liquid cash by which they are expected to buy any commodity and market it to their customers.(the crowd in general).
</item>
        <item >Students (participants) should not use mobiles during event rounds.
Since the tasks will be given to the group of students as a whole, each member in the group should participate in the rounds.
\nFor selling, convincing and marketing students should not cheat by taking some money from friends or any other sources or adding their own money. And if they do, then the event heads have the right to disqualify them.
In convincing round, participants should not force or give mental or any physical stress to the students.
Proper bills have to be maintained for the commodities purchased.

            
        </item>
        <item >Kajal Panchal 		+91 9619441189
\nSamruddhi Kuchik 	+91 9594935472
            
        </item>
        <item>for more information visit: http://technovanza.org/scam.php</item>
        </string-array>
		
		<string-array name="webpreneur">
        <item >
            Mark Zuckerberg (Founder of Facebook), Sachin and BinnyBansal (Flipkart), stupidsid.com (Founded by students of DJ Sanghvi).....ever seen these sites and thought, Hell! I could have thought of it, he just got there first! All these extremely popular and innovative websites were made by students just like YOU! All they had was a brief idea of they wanted; they all started small and rose into the popularity ranks quickly! If you have an idea or you are a coding maestro this is for you! 

\nTEAM SPECIFICATION :
\nA team should consist of a maximum of 2 participants (coders + ideators). Students from different educational institutes can form a team.
\nA single participate can also register. The coders and the ideators will be grouped accordingly by us.

\nCERTIFICATE POLICY: 
\n1. Certificate of appreciation or participation will be awarded to the all teams. And certificate of   excellence will be given to the top two teams. 
\n2. Disqualified teams will not be considered for any certificates.
\nCash Prize of 12,000 INR to be won.
\n Certificates will be given on the spot.
\nFREE Registrations for all events and non-commercial exhibitions.
            
         </item>
        <item> 
 			 The WEB-PRENEUR is an entrepreneurial event in which you pluggin your skills in creativity, coding and entrepreneurship to develop a website or more precisely an online business firm in a few hours using any of the web development language you prefer and feel comfortable with HTML/ CSS ,PHP , JSP.
Webpreneur is basically a managerial competition initiated by the Entrepreneurship Cell on the technical lines in which the participants will be grouped in teams of two, each team having a coder and an ideator who will have to work in mutual harmony to build their website.In a span of 6hrs every team is expected to create a website based start-up (not product based).
Contestants will be provided with the necessary infrastructure you need for the coding and developing of   	the website

\nThe event will be conducted in three rounds:
\nROUND 1:
\nThe first and the primary round is where you have to submit or present the idea of your website to the judges. Rankings would be given on the basis of how your idea is more feasible to sustain the downs of the market, profitability , the investments you have to make and how you would be contributing to the socio-economic purpose. Also, the technical knowledge of the coder will also be accounted for.

\nROUND 2:
\nThose qualifying for the first round on the basis of the scores will actually get the opportunity to code their websites in round II.
The second round being the actual backbone where you actually build your website.
You have maximum of 6 hours to put up your virtual reality!

\nROUND 3:
\nThe third round is where you give a presentation of your website and explain how efficient and productive your business plan would be when you launch it. There also will be a questionnare to test the genuinity of your work. eg. You will be made to debug your codes on putting errors onto it .
            
    	</item>
        <item >\n1.	Any case found of copying the source-codes will be disqualified .
\n2.	A hard-coder will be preferred over CMS users (jhoomla,wordpress) 
\n3.	Websites publicizing any particular brand will not be allowed.
            
        </item>
        <item >Pratik Sutar 		+91 9821275515 	
\nAnushri Bhagwat 	+91 7208317083 	
            
        </item>
        <item>for more information visit: http://technovanza.org/webpreneur.php</item>
        </string-array>
</resources>